原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     秋乙一   eunice  子V   Alex
翻译     Johnny G   huiyi   安尘
翻译     静妹粒   Margaery   秋明月
校对     小早   杏仁斯嘉丽   彼岸的宁静
时间轴     Avis   Ans   纸袋p   cci小白   魚鱼鱼
后期     8T
总监     somehacker   小早
♪《夏日最后的玫瑰》(The Last Rose Of Summer)
*这是夏日最后一支玫瑰*
*'Tis the last rose of summer*
*独自盛放*
*Left blooming alone*
*往昔迷人的伙伴*
*All her lovely companions*
*均已凋谢消散*
*Are faded and gone*
*再无花朵相伴*
*No flower of her kindred*
三块广告牌
*再无花蕾相陪*
*No rosebud is nigh*
*映衬她的红润*
*To reflect back her blushes*
*应和她的忧愁*
*And give sigh for sigh*
艾彬镇广告公司
你是瑞德·韦尔比吗
You Red Welby?
是的  女士  您有何贵干
Yes, ma'am. How may I help you?
我听说饮水路上有三块广告牌
I hear those three billboards out on Drinkwater Road.
你负责把它们租出去  对吧
You're in charge of renting 'em out, that right?
我都不知道我们在饮水路上有广告牌
I didn't know we had any billboards out on Drinkwater Roa...
饮水路在哪儿
Where is Drinkwater Road?
在过了赛兹莫尔路的岔路上
It's the road out past Sizemore turn-off.
高速路通了后就没人走那儿了
Nobody uses it since the freeway got put in.
你说得没错
You're right.
我们在那儿还真有三块广告牌
We got three billboards out there.
从1986年后就没人租过了
Nobody's put nothing up out there since 1986.
最后一任租客是好奇纸尿裤
That was Huggies.
三块广告牌租一年多少钱
How much to rent all three of them out for the year?
一年吗
A year?
那里平时根本没人去
You wanna pay for three billboards
去的人要么迷路了要么就是傻子
on a road that no one goes down
你竟然想租那三块广告牌
unless they got lost or they're retards...
一次租一年吗
for a year?
你可真聪明  是吧  韦尔比
Quick, ain't you, Welby?
既然现在艾彬镇广告
Since what I say goes these days
办公室里是我说了算
down at the Ebbing Advertising desk,
那三块广告牌  我会给你个好价钱
I'm gonna strike you a real good deal on those billboards.
女士  您的名字是什么
Now, what was it your name was, Missus...
有法律规定说广告牌上不能写什么吗
What's the law on what you can and cannot say on a billboard?
我想诽谤的话肯定不行
I assume you can't say nothing defamatory,
妈的  傻屌  贱逼  这些也不行对吧
and you can't say, "Fuck," "Piss," Or "Cunt." That right?
还有
Or...
爆菊  也不行
"...anus."
那我没什么问题了
Well, I think I'll be all right then.
这是第一个月的五千美元租金
Here's 5,000 for the first month.
应该够了吧
I assume that'll cover it.
这是广告牌上要写的东西
And here's what the billboards are to say.
在做的时候  你起草一份合同
Why don't you write up a contract betwixt us while you're at it,
确保没人能在我的租期内把广告牌租走
make sure nobody rents them billboards out from under me.
我想你就是安吉拉·海斯的母亲了
I guess you're Angela Hayes's mother.
没错  我是安吉拉·海斯的母亲
That's right. I'm Angela Hayes's mother.
我叫米尔德里德
Name's Mildred.
艾彬镇警察局
广告牌多久才能做好
How long before you get 'em put up?
不然就
Shall we say by...
复活节的周日行吗
...Easter Sunday?
再好不过了
That'd be perfect.
当我走在拉雷多街上的那一刻
As I was walking down the streets of Laredo
在我走向拉雷多的那一天
As I walked down to Laredo one day
我看到位年轻牛仔  一身白色亚麻
I spied a young cowboy all wrapped in white linen
一身白色亚麻
All wrapped in white linen
冷如黏土
And cold as the clay
怎么搞的  威洛比局长
-这他妈是什么  -什么
- Hey, what the hell is this? - Que?
"怎么搞的  威洛比局长"是什么
"How come, Chief Willoughby" what?
-是什么  -对啊
- What? - Yeah.
"怎么搞的"然后呢
"How come" what?
-然后什么  -什么
- What, what? - What?
听着  你这墨西哥佬
Listen, you fucking beaner,
你最好快点给我解释
I'd better start getting some straight answers outta you.
放下
Put that down.
依然无人被捕
密苏里州艾彬镇警察
这他妈是什么
What the hell is this?
依然无人被捕
你过来  这他妈是什么鬼
Hey, you. What the fuck is this?
什么"他妈是什么"
What the fuck is what?
这个  就这个
This! This.
-我想是广告  -什么广告
- Advertising, I guess. - Advertising what?
某些搞不懂的东西
Something obscure?
可不是嘛
I'll say. Yeah.
我在哪儿见过你吗
Don't I know your face from some place?
-我不知道  你见过我吗  -见过
- I don't know, do you? - Yeah. Yeah, I do.
我现在就可以逮捕你
I could arrest you right now if I wanted to.
-理由呢  -因为你在这乱倒垃圾
- For what? - For emptying your bucket there.
这违反了  违反了
That's... that's against the...
这不对  违反了环境法
...being bad, against the environment laws.
迪克逊警官  在你逮捕我之前
Well, before you do that, Officer Dixon.
你不如往前走
How about you go have
去第一个广告牌那儿看看
yourself a look at that first billboard over there?
然后我们再好好谈谈
And then we can have ourself a conversation
什么狗屁环境法
about the motherfucking environment.
如何
How about that?
这他妈的
Fuck me.
别接  威廉
Don't, William.
迪克逊  你的天杀的混蛋
Dixon, you goddamn asshole.
我可是正在吃复活节晚餐
I'm in the middle of my goddamn Easter dinner.
抱歉  孩子们
Sorry, kids.
我知道  局长
I know, Chief,
很抱歉打到家里来  但是
and I'm sorry for calling you at home and all, but...
我觉得我们有麻烦了
...I think we got kind of a problem.
有人惨遭奸杀
依然无人被捕
怎么搞的  威洛比局长
有人惨遭奸杀
依然无人被捕
♪《鹿皮种马蓝调》(Buckskin Stallion Blues)
*我听见她银铃般的歌声*
*I heard her sing in tongues of silver*
*我听见她在夏日暴雨中的哭声*
*I heard her cry on a summer storm*
*我爱过她  但她不曾得知*
*I loved her, but she did not know it*
*因此我再不去想她*
*So I don't think about her anymore*
*现在她离我而去  我不敢相信*
*Now she's gone, and I can't believe it*
*因此我再不去想她*
*So I don't think about her anymore*
*如果三加四只等于七*
*If three and four was seven only*
*那又置一加二于何地*
*Where would that leave one and two*
*如果爱只意味着寂寞*
*If love can be and still be lonely*
不不不  你们回去
No, no. No, no. Go back.
*那又置你我于何地*
*Where does that leave me and you*
*过去的时光  将来的日子*
*Time there was, and time there will be*
*又置你我于何地*
*Where does that leave me and you*
抱歉我迟到了  丹妮丝
Sorry I'm late, Denise.
那些对付警察的广告牌弄好了吗
Did you put up those billboards to fuck with the cops yet?
竖起来了
They're up.
干得漂亮  姑娘  给那些警察点教训
You go, girl. You go fuck those cops up.
你以为自己在干嘛  韦尔比
What the fuck do you think you're doing, Welby,
搞出那种广告牌
...a bunch of billboards like that?
你就不怕有什么法律后果吗
You didn't think there'd be some kind of ramifications, legally?
什么法律后果  塞德里克
What's the legal ramifications, Cedric?
你凭什么让我解释法律后果
You want me to explain legal ramifications,
你个混小子  别叫我塞德里克
...little punk like you? And don't call me Cedric!
这没有违反任何法律和规定
Ain't contravening no laws on propriety.
不违法  也他妈的不违反其他任何东西
Ain't contravening no laws on any fucking thing.
我都查过了
I checked all this out.
你又是在哪儿查的
And where'd you check all this out?
在一本
In a...
-一本书里  -什么书啊  大天才
- ...a book. - Which book, genius?
一本叫《去你妈的关你屁事》的书
Book called Suck My Ass, It's None Of Your Business.
我去
Fuck.
这个人  或者这群人
How long has this person, or persons,
租了广告牌多长时间
...rented these billboards out for?
一年
Oh... the year.
她付了多长时间的租金
How long has she actually paid for?
一年
The year.
所以是个女的  没错吧
So it's a "She", is it?
我无权泄露客户信息  局长
I ain't at liberty to divulge that kind of information, Chief.
是不是米尔德里德·海斯呢
Mildred Hayes, perhaps?
我无权泄露客户信息  局长
Ain't at liberty to divulge that kind of information, Chief.
你真的愿意招惹艾彬警察局吗  瑞德
Do you really wanna fuck with the Ebbing Police Department, Red?
你敢吗
Do you?
或许吧
I guess.
他真这么说吗  当着你面说的
He said what? To your face?
现在还没人有罪
No crime has been committed here.
不是吧  难道诋毁人格就不是罪吗
Oh, come on. Defamation of character ain't a crime?
她若只是提问就不能算诋毁
It isn't defamation if she's simply asking a question.
怎么  你是白痴吗
What are you, an idiot?
不许叫我白痴  迪克逊
Don't call me an idiot, Dixon!
我没叫你白痴
I didn't call you an idiot.
我问你是不是白痴  提问而已
I asked if you was an idiot. That was a question.
-你被他套进去了  塞德里克  -就这样吗  快点
- He got you there, Cedric.  - That's it? Come on, man!
别发脾气啊
Hey! Don't go flying off the handle.
你为什么要雇用他
Why in the hell you keep that man on?
他本质上是个好人
He's a good man at heart.
他拷打过被拘押的人  比尔
He tortured a guy in custody, Bill.
没有...确切证据证明那是真的
There was no... real evidence to support that.
撤下来
Take 'em down.
-什么  -把那玩意撤下来
- Huh? - Take that shit down.
把什么玩意撤下来
Take what shit down?
小子  你以为我不会
Hey, boy. You think I wouldn't
在大马路上把你揍趴下吗  瑞德
take you out right here on Main Street, Red?
我还以为你只揍黑人呢  迪克逊
I thought you only took out black dudes, Dixon.
不  不  住手
No! No! Stop it.
你敢动我一根汗毛试试  混蛋
You ever fucking touch me, motherfucker...
你喝醉了吗
You drunk?
-这么早就醉了啊  -起来
- Are you drunk right now? - Get up.
反正那条路也没人会走
Nobody ever goes down that road anyways.
除非迷路了  或者脑子有病
Unless they got lost. Or they're retards.
最重要是别紧张
Well, don't be nervous, is the main thing.
会很顺利的
It'll go just fine.
当然了  别看镜头
Don't look in the camera, obviously.
等这辆车过了就开始
Let's hold for this car.
倒数三  二  一
In three, two, one.
米尔德里德·海斯  你为何竖起这些广告牌
So, Mildred Hayes, why did you put up these billboards?
我的女儿  安吉拉
My daughter, Angela,
在七个月前被绑架并遭到奸杀
...was abducted, raped and murdered seven months ago...
就在这条路上
...along this selfsame stretch of road.
你在看什么  妈妈  破新闻吗
What you watching, Momma? Stupid news?
在我看来  本地警察
It seems to me the local police department...
整天忙着到处拷打黑人
...is too busy going around torturing black folks...
完全没有心思去侦破真正的罪案
...to be bothered doing anything about solving actual crime.
我想着这些广告牌也许能让他们集中精力
I thought these billboards might concentrate their minds some.
操
Fuck.
老实说  我不知道警察都在干什么
I don't know what the police are doing, to be honest with you.
我只知道我女儿烧焦的尸体
I do know that my, daughter's burnt body is,
依然无人被捕
被埋在六尺之下
lying six feet underground.
而警察们每天只是吃甜甜圈
All they're doing is eating Krispy Kremes...
和抓在停车场溜冰的小屁孩
...and busting eight-year-olds for skating around parking lots.
那威洛比局长
And Chief Willoughby,
为何要专门提到他
...why single him out?
他是警察的头儿  不是吗
He's the head of them, ain't he?
必须有人来承担责任
The buck's gotta stop somewhere.
所以该由威洛比负责吗
And the buck stops at Willoughby?
没错  该由威洛比负责
Yeah, the buck stops at Willoughby.
绝对是这样
Dead right it does.
你还好吧
You all right there, fella?
看来我们有一场硬仗要打
Looks like we got a war on our hands.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
只要能抓住凶手  什么我都愿意做  海斯夫人
I'd do anything to catch the guy who did it, Mrs. Hayes.
但犯人DNA与有案底的犯人都不匹配
But when the DNA, don't match no one who's ever been arrested,
与全国范围内的犯罪记录也不匹配
...and when the DNA, don't match any other crime nationwide,
在她离开你家
...and when, there wasn't a single eyewitness...
到我们发现她这段时间内  又没有目击证人
from the time she'd left your house,to the time we found her, well...
眼下我们能做的实在有限
...right now there ain't too much more we can do.
你们可以抽取镇上所有
Could pull blood from every man and boy in this town...
八岁以上男性的血样
...over the age of eight.
民权法不允许这么做  海斯夫人
There's civil rights laws prevents that, Mrs. Hayes.
再说如果凶手只是路过小镇呢
And what if he was just passing through town?
那就抽取全国所有男性的血样
Pull blood from every man in the country, then.
那要是他只是路过这个国家呢
Then what if he was just passing through the country?
换做我的话  我会建立一个资料库
If it was me, I'd start up a database.
每个男婴儿出生  都要留下记录
Every male baby what's born, stick them on it,
等他犯罪后
...and as soon as he done something wrong,
就交叉对比
...cross-reference it,
百分百确认匹配后
...make 100% certain it was a correct match,
就杀了他
...then kill him.
好吧  这个
Yeah, well, there's...
民权法也是坚决禁止的
...definitely civil rights laws prevents that.
我已经竭尽所能追查凶手了
I'm doing everything I can to track him down.
我觉得那些广告牌不太公平
I don't think those, billboards is very fair.
就在你来这里
The time it took you
找我抱怨这会儿  威洛比
to get out here whining like a bitch, Willoughby,
也许就有
...some other poor girl's
其他可怜的女孩正被屠杀
probably out there being butchered right now.
你可真能分得清轻重缓急啊
But I'm glad you got your priorities straight,
了不起
I'll say that for you.
还有一件事  米尔德里德
There's something else, Mildred.
我得了癌症
I got cancer.
-我快死了  -我知道
- I'm dying. - I know it.
我知道  镇上大部分人都知道
I know it. Most everybody in town knows it.
那你还竖那些广告牌
And you still put up, those billboards?
你死了之后  广告牌就没那么有效果了  对吧
Well, they wouldn't be as effective after you croak. Right?
瞧啊
Well, looky looky.
这不正是
If it ain't the instigator
整件破事的煽动者吗
of this whole goddamn affair in the first place.
我才没煽动什么  迪克逊
I didn't instigate shit, Dixon.
跟镇上的小矮子打桌球
Playing pool against the town midget.
他说得对  瑞德
He's right, Red,
你在跟镇上的小矮子打桌球
...you are playing pool against the town midget.
是啊  他是警察  观察力很敏锐的
You know, he's a cop. You know, he's observant.
我一向都不喜欢你  瑞德
I always disliked you, Red,
打从你还是个挂着鼻涕的小屁孩开始
...ever since you was a snotty little child.
你现在仍然像个挂着鼻涕的小屁孩
You still look like a snotty little child.
真可惜  我一直觉得你很棒
That's unfortunate. I always thought you was great.
连你的名字  瑞德·韦尔比
Even your name, Red Welby.
连你的名字我都不喜欢
Even your name I disliked.
好吧
Well...okay.
听起来就像你是共党似的
Like you was some kind of goddamn communist or something...
-还很自豪  -不  是因为我有一头红发
- ...and proud of it. - No, it's 'cause I got red hair.
你知道他们在古巴如何对待基佬吗  韦尔比
You know what they do to faggots down in Cuba, Welby?
思维真够跳跃的
Wow, that's left field.
古巴人到底如何对待基佬呢  迪克逊
No, what do they do to faggots down in Cuba, Dixon?
杀了他们
They kill 'em.
你也许会感到意外  但我反对这种做法
Which, it might surprise you to learn, I'm against.
我不确定在古巴基佬是否真的会被杀死  迪克逊
I'm not sure if they do kill faggots down in Cuba, Dixon.
我知道就同性恋来说
I know Cuba's human rights record's pretty deplorable...
古巴的人权记录很悲惨
...when it comes to homosexuality,
但严重到杀人
...but killing 'em?
你确定你想的不是怀俄明州吗
Are you sure you ain't thinking of Wyoming?
你总是喜欢抖机灵
Always with the smart-ass. Jesus.
球打得不错  对吧
He's quite good, isn't he?
威洛比是个好人  看着我  你看着我
Hey, Willoughby's a good man. Hey, look at me. Hey, look at me.
我好声好气地跟你说话
I'm talking nice to you now, aren't I?
好声好气的
I'm talking nice to you.
威洛比是个好人  瑞德
Willoughby's a good man, Red.
不该让他为这种事烦心
Shouldn't have this be the only thing he thinks about,
他只剩下几个月了
...last months left to him.
只剩什么几个月
Last months what?
你...
Oh, you...
你不知道吗
...you didn't know?
他得了胰腺癌
Yeah, pancre... pancreatic.
下一个到我  你们俩娘们别逼逼了
I'm up next. You old ladies quit yakking.
-真没礼貌  -米尔德里德
- Rude. - Hey, Mildred.
我前几天在电视上看到你了
I saw you on TV the other day.
-是吗  -嗯  你看起来不错
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah, you looked good.
我意思是  你表现得很好
I mean, you know, you came across really good...
你要说的那些话
...in the things that you were saying.
我觉得你表现得不好
I didn't think you came across real good.
我觉得你听起来...  你看上去很蠢
I think you sounded... you came across as a stupid-ass.
这个点儿你不是该回家找你妈了吗  迪克逊
Ain't it about time you got home to your momma, Dixon?
不  这个点儿我还不用回家找我妈  妈妈
No, it ain't time I go home to my mama... momma.
我跟她说了我要出来  十二点才回去
I told her I was gonna be out, till 12:00, actually.
天呐
Jesus.
剩下你我对阵了  米尔德里德
That's me versus you, Mildred.
罗比  那个小矮子好像对我有意思
Hey, Robbie. I think that midget wants to get in my pants.
蒙哥马利神父
Father Montgomery.
米尔德里德  很抱歉
Mildred. I'm... I'm sorry
我这么晚还来打扰  但是
to be calling on you so late, but, uh...
我得说  罗比把我招待得很好
...I must say, Robbie has been the, consummate host.
虽然他刚跟我说
Despite his having had, as he was just telling me,
今天在学校挺难熬的
...somewhat of a tricky day at school.
不  只是球队有些人找我麻烦
Oh, no. Just some of the guys on the team was giving me crap.
找什么麻烦
Crap about what?
因为那些广告牌  米尔德里德
About the billboards, Mildred.
我来也是为了跟你谈谈这事
Which is what I've come to have a word with you about.
说吧
Oh. Proceed.
我知道过去一年对你来说
I know how hard, it's been for you, Mildred,
很艰难  我们都清楚
...this past year. We all do.
如果日后你有任何需要
And if there is ever anything, that you need,
我们都会陪在你身边  随时随地
...we will be there for you. Always.
但镇上的人也很清楚
But the town also knows...
威廉·威洛比的人品
...what kind of a man, William Willoughby is.
全镇都极力反对你的广告牌
And the town is dead set against these billboards of yours.
你做民意调查了吗  神父
Took a poll, did you, Father?
米尔德里德  如果你仍然来教堂
You know, Mildred, if you hadn't stopped coming to church,
你就会更清楚
...you'd have a little bit more understanding...
人们内心的想法
...of the depth of people's feelings.
周日有十几个人来找过我
I had more than a dozen people come up to me on Sunday.
所以是的  我做过民意调查
So, yes, I took a poll.
安吉拉的事  大家都与你同在
Everybody is with you, about Angela.
但广告牌的事没人支持你
Nobody is with you about this.
你知道我今天在想什么吗
You know what I was thinking about today?
我想到了那两支
I was thinking about those street gangs...
在洛杉矶的街头帮派
...they have down in Los Angeles,
瘸帮和血帮
...those Crips and those Bloods.
我还想到了在八十年代
And I was thinking about that bunch of new laws...
政府颁布的一系列新法
...they came up with in the 1980s,
应该是为了打击那些街头帮派
I think it was, ...to combat those street gangs,
这些瘸帮和血帮的混混
those Crips and those Bloods.
如果我没记错的话
And, if I remember rightly,
那一系列新法的重点就是
the gist of what those new laws were saying was,
如果你加入了其中一支帮派  和他们鬼混
...if you join one of these gangs, and you're running with them,
某晚你走在街上  你不知道在什么时候
...and down the block one night, unbeknownst to you,
你的瘸帮或是血帮同伙
...one of your fellow Crips, or your fellow Bloods,
在附近开枪或者拿刀捅人
...shoot up a place, or stab a guy...
就算你可能对此毫不知情
...well then, even though you may not know nothing about it...
就算你可能
...and even though you may
只是站在了街角处
have just been standing on a street corner,
做着自己的事情
...minding your own business...
新法还是会判你有罪
What these new laws said was, you're still culpable.
你会因为加入了瘸帮或血帮
You're still culpable by the very act of having joined...
这个行为就被判有罪
...those Crips and those Bloods in the first place.
神父  这不禁让我想到
Which got me thinking, Father...
这种情况
...that whole type of situation...
不就和你们教会很像吗
...is kinda like you church boys, ain't it?
你们有自己的旗子  活动场所
You got your colors, you got your clubhouse.
怎么说呢  你们也是个帮派
You're, for want of a better word, a gang.
如果你在楼上边抽烟边读《圣经》
And if you were upstairs smoking a pipe and reading your Bible...
与此同时  你的帮派成员
...while one of your fellow gang members...
正在楼下猥亵祭坛男童  那...
...is downstairs fucking an altar boy, well...
神父  你就像那些瘸帮和血帮成员一样
Father, just like those Crips, and just like those Bloods,
你也有罪
...you're culpable...
因为你加入了这个帮派
...'cause you joined the gang, man.
我不管你有没有做过
I don't care if you never did shit,
看见过  或是听说过这种破事
...you never saw shit, you never heard shit.
你加入了帮派  你就有罪
You join the gang, you're culpable.
当一个人因为猥亵祭坛男童
And when a person is culpable, to altar-boy-fucking,
或是猥亵任何男童被判有罪时
...or any kinda boy-fucking,
我知道你们这些人不怎么挑
...'cause I know you guys didn't really narrow that down...
这种人没资格进入我家
...then you kinda forfeit the right to come into my house...
干涉我和我的生活
...and say anything about me, or my life,
对我的女儿和我的广告牌指手画脚
...or my daughter, or my billboards.
您先把茶喝完吧  神父
So why don't you just finish up your tea there, Father,
然后滚出我的厨房
...and get the fuck outta my kitchen.
还是谢谢您的拜访  神父
But thanks for coming up anyway, Father.
感觉怎么样  比尔
How you been feeling, Bill?
感觉像是我的一个主要器官得了癌症
Ah, like I got cancer in a major organ.
我只想告诉你  关于米尔德里德·海斯的事
Well, I just want you to know we're all on your side...
我们都站在你这边
...about this Mildred Hayes thing.
如果我再他妈听到有人跟我说这句话
If I have to hear that one more fucking time...
我受够了  我不想浪费生命等待
I'm done with this shit. I can't waste my life waiting.
别他妈看漫画书了
Stop reading fucking comic books...
把海斯的案卷拿给我
...and get me the file on the Hayes case.
是安吉拉的还是米尔德里德的
Angela Hayes case or the Mildred Hayes case?
根本没有米尔德里德·海斯的案卷
There is no Mildred Hayes case.
我们收到了两起
We've had two official complaints...
对广告牌的正式投诉  所以...
...about those billboards, so, actually...
谁投诉的
From who?
一只眼睛很可笑的女人
There's a lady with a funny eye...
还有个胖牙医
...and a fat dentist.
把安吉拉·海斯的案卷给我
Get me the file on the Angela Hayes case.
"一只眼睛很可笑的女人"
"A lady with a funny fucking eye"?
老天
Jesus Christ.
又喝到很晚
Late night?
没
No.
别去找韦尔比的麻烦了行吗
Lay off that Welby guy, will you?
我要是不听呢
Or you'll do what?
把你妈妈的牙齿都踢碎
Kick your momma's fucking teeth in.
你不会这么做的
No, you won't.
谁告诉你我找他麻烦了  那个小矮子吗
Who told you I was laying on him anyway? The midget?
你他妈在说些什么啊
What the fuck are you talking about?
我还想在这里专心办案
And I'm trying to fucking concentrate.
去他的小矮子
Fucking midgets!
怎么搞的  威洛比局长
你这是在找什么啊
What you looking for anyway?
这里什么都没有啊
There's nothing to look for.
我不知道是怎么回事
I don't know what it is.
感觉这个牙松动了
It feels like it's kinda waggling.
如果松动的话  就得拔出来
Well, if it's waggling, it's gonna have to come out.
你难道不要先看看吗
Ain't you gonna take a look at it first?
一定要拔掉
It's gonna have to come out.
能给我打点麻药吗  医生
Can I get a little Novocaine there, Doc?
等个几分钟
Give it a couple of minutes.
我只是想说这镇上很多人
I just wanted to say there's a lot of good friends...
都是比尔·威洛比的好朋友  海斯夫人
...of Bill Willoughby in this town, Miss Hayes.
不要  住手  快住手
No! Ow! Stop! No!
该死的
God damn it!
那你去告诉比尔·威洛比的那些好朋友
Then why don't you tell those good friends of Bill Willoughby...
要他做好自己那该死的工作  死胖子
...to tell him to go do his fucking job, fat boy.
你好啊  米尔德里德
Hey there, Mildred.
今天去看牙医的人
You didn't happen to pay a, visit...
不会碰巧是你吧
...to the dentist today, did you?
不是
No.
我说了  不是
I said, "No."
那不是你在肥仔杰弗里的
Oh, so it wasn't you who drilled a little hole...
肥大指甲盖上钻了个小洞咯
...in one of big fat Geoffrey's big fat thumbnails, no?
当然不是
Of course not.
我说了  当然不是
I said, "Of course not."
你在牙医手上钻了个洞
You drilled a hole in the dentist?
我没有  丹妮丝
Denise, no, I didn't.
我自己还是觉得挺好笑的  不过
I thought it was kinda funny myself, but...
他想告你
...he wants to press charges,
恐怕我们得把你带进局子里了
...so we're gonna have to bring you in, I'm afraid.
近来黑鬼折磨事业进展如何  迪克逊
So how's it all going in the nigger-torturing business, Dixon?
我们现在都说折磨有色人种
It's persons-of-color-torturing business, these days.
你要真想知道的话
If you wanna know...
我谁都没折磨
...I didn't torture nobody.
你在电视上说那些话是有什么毛病啊
What's the matter with you, saying that goddamn, stuff on TV?
我妈妈经常看那个台的
My momma watches that station.
你妈妈不知道你折磨人的事吗
Your momma doesn't know about the torturing?
她一点都不知道
No, she doesn't know anything about it.
她反对那样做
She's against that kinda thing.
谁反对什么
Who's against what?
我妈妈...反对折磨有色人种
My mama... momma is against persons-of-color-torturing.
她说的是"折磨黑鬼"
She said, "Nigger-torturing."
我说"现在不能再说折磨黑鬼了"
I said, "You can't say nigger-torturing' no more."
"你得说折磨有色人种"
"You gotta say persons-of-color-torturing."
我说得对吗  局长
Isn't that right, Chief?
说得对吗
Ain't that right?
接下来让我一个人来处理
I think I'll be able to, take care of Mrs. Hayes...
海斯夫人的事就行  杰森
...on my own from here on, Jason.
好的局长  我就在外面
Sure, Chief. I'll be right outside.
别那副表情看我
Don't give me that look.
如果你想除掉每个有种族歧视倾向的警察
If you got rid of every cop with vaguely racist leanings,
那局里只会留下三个警察
...you'd have... three cops left,
而这三个还都讨厌基佬
...and all of them are gonna hate the fags.
到时候你又该怎么办呢
So what are you gonna do, you know?
我想问你件事  米尔德里德
I wanna know something, Mildred.
你为什么要在那可怜的
Why'd you drill a hole...
肥仔杰弗里的指甲盖上钻洞呢
...through poor fat Geoffrey's thumbnail?
没那回事
That did not happen.
他手滑了一下
His hand slipped.
不小心在自己手上钻了个洞
He drilled a hole through his own self.
他说是我干的吗
Did he say I did it?
看来我们俩的口供不一致啊
I guess it's his word against mine, then, huh?
有点像你听说的那些强奸案
Kinda like in all those rape cases you hear about.
只不过这次女人没有输
Except, this time, the chick ain't losing.
这其实跟输赢无关吧  是吗  米尔德里德
It ain't really about winning or losing, though, is it, Mildred?
你觉得我会关心你们两个谁输谁赢吗
You think I, care about who wins or loses between the two of youse?
你觉得我会关心牙医吗
You think I care about dentists?
我根本就不关心什么牙医
I don't care about dentists.
没人会关心牙医
Nobody cares about dentists.
我关心的  或者说
What I do care about, or what I'm...
我感兴趣的是
...interested in...
让你在法庭里脱不了身
...is tying you up in court so long...
占用掉你你在礼品店工作的大半时间
...that your hours at the gift shop be so shot to shit...
导致你身上没有一分钱
...that you ain't gonna have a penny...
来付广告牌下个月的租金
...to pay for another month's billboards.
-我存了些...  -我感兴趣的是这个
- I got some dough put... - That's what I'm interested in.
我存了些钱
I got some dough put away.
但我听说的是
But what I heard,
你不得不卖掉你前夫的牵引拖车
was you had to sell off your ex-husband's tractor-trailer...
才勉强租了这个月的广告牌  对吗
...to even pay for this month's billboards, that right?
对了  老查理最近怎么样
How is old Charlie, by the way?
还是在和那个
He still shacked up with
在动物园实习的小美女同居吗
that pretty little intern works down at the zoo?
是和闻起来一股屎味的妞同居
He's still shacked up with some chick smells of shit.
我不知道是不是她在动物园工作的原因
I don't know if the zoo's got anything to do with it.
希望是如此
Although I'd hope so.
她多大了  十九岁
How old is she? Nineteen?
肯定很聪明吧
That must smart.
继续说  你继续说
Keep trying. Keep trying.
查理是怎么看你这几块广告牌的
What's Charlie think about these here billboards of yours,
他以前可是个警察呢
...an ex-cop like, Charlie?
前任警察  家暴前夫  一个样不是吗
Ex-cop, ex-wife-beater. Same difference, I guess, right?
看来这次是他和你各执其词了对吧
His word against yours, though, right?
查理不知道广告牌的事对吗
Charlie don't know about 'em, does he?
不关他的事
It's none of his business.
不过好像是他付的钱  不是吗
Well, he's kinda paying for 'em, though, ain't he?
-是我付的  -这个月是你付的
- I'm paying for 'em! - This month you are.
那到...
How about when...
-我不是故意的  -我知道
- I...I didn't mean to... - I know.
-这是个意外  -我知道  亲爱的
- It was an accident. - I know, baby.
是血
It's blood.
我去叫人
I'm gonna go get somebody.
-放她走吧  -别啊  局长
- Just let her go. - Come on, Chief.
放她走
Just let her go!
慢点  慢点  慢点
Easy, easy, easy.
鸟会得癌症吗
Do birds get cancer?
我说鸟  会不会得癌症
Birds. Do they get cancer?
我不知道  我知道狗会
I don't know. Dogs do.
好吧  我又没说狗  对吧
Yeah, well, I wasn't talking about dogs, was I?
这下好了  又是这条"惨遭奸杀"的回家路
Great, the good old "Raped While Dying" route home.
因为如果一天中有那么两秒
Cause if there was two seconds in a day...
我没想着她
when I wasn't thinking about her
没想着她是怎么死的
and I wasn't thinking about how she died,
"快看啊  再多想想  为什么不呢"
"There you go! Think about it some more, why don't you?"
这也好  虽然一个人竭力避免
It's good too, that as much as a person might have tried...
回想那件事的细节
to avoid the details of what happened...
因为他觉得这样没什么好处
'cause he didn't think it would do any good,
他觉得忍受不了
and he didn't think he could bear it...
能够这样被提醒可真不错
it's also good to be informed...
用二十英尺高的漂亮字体
in 20-foot-high font and in real nice lettering...
提醒人们她生命最后时刻的生动细节
the precise details, of her last moments.
知道她被强奸了还不够
That it wasn't enough that she was raped...
知道她死了还不够  不行
and it wasn't enough that she died, no.
非要"惨遭奸杀"
"Raped While Dying."
真谢谢你了  老妈
Thank you, Mom.
我给过你警方报告了
I gave you the police reports.
我没看
I didn't read 'em.
这事我已经够抑郁的了
I'm depressed enough as it fucking is.
危险
妈
Mom?
怎么啦
Yeah?
你今晚该不会又要出门吧
You ain't going out again tonight, are ya?
要出门  丹妮丝和我要喝点啤酒
Denise and I are gonna grab a couple of beers, yeah.
丹妮丝开车接送你吗
Denise gonna be driving you?
安吉拉  你为什么不直接问我能不能借车
Angela, Why don't you just ask me if you can borrow the car?
-我能借车吗  -不行
- Can I borrow the car? - No.
-贱人  -我给你钱打车
- Bitch! - I will give you money for a taxi...
只要你好好说话而且别管我叫贱人
if you ask me nice and don't call me a bitch.
如果你不打算借我
Why'd you make me ask you to borrow it
为什么还让我问你
if you was never gonna let me borrow it?
因为有趣  还有因为你整天吸大麻
'Cause it was funny! And because you've been smoking pot all day.
-你真是个伪君子  -伪君子
- You are such a hypocrite. - Hypocrite?
-是的  -怎么说
- Yeah. - How?
我们小时候  你酒驾载我们
You drove drunk with us in the car when we were kids.
-你胡说什么呢  -爸爸告诉我的
- What are you talking about? - Daddy told me.
-你什么时候去见他的  -不要转移话题
- When'd you see him? - Don't change the subject.
你到底有没有在我们小时候
Did you or did you not drive drunk with us
酒驾载我们
in the car when we were kids?
-可能就一次  -行  就一次吗
- Once, maybe. - Okay, once?
当时他把我打得半死
When he was in the middle of beating the shit out of me.
我们听的都是你一面之词
Which we've only got your word about, right?
安吉拉  看在老天的份上
Angela, for Christ sakes.
你为什么从不站在我这边  罗比
Why are you never on my side, Robbie?
你没那么贱逼的时候我都站在你这边
I'm always on your side when you're not being a cunt!
在家里不许再说贱逼
There will be no more "cunts..." ...in this house.
你明白了吗  先生
You got that, mister?
怎么  你要搬出去吗
What, are you moving out?
我说着玩的
It was a ga... it's a ga... it was a gag.
你到底借不借我车
Are you gonna let me borrow the car or what?
要不你走着去  安吉拉  走着去啊
Why don't you just walk, Angela? Why don't you just walk?
你知道吗  我就走着去了
You know what? I will walk.
我走着去  还有你知道吗
I will walk! And you know what else?
-我希望我路上被强奸  -我也希望
- I hope I get raped on the way! - Yeah, well, I hope...
你路上被强奸
you get raped on the way too!
怎么搞的  威洛比局长
我们要你留院观察几天  比尔
We're gonna need to keep you in a few days, Bill.
你不该一直咳血的
You shouldn't be coughing up blood.
是啊  我猜也是  医生
Yeah. Kinda guessed that, Doc.
我早上再来吧
I'll swing by in the morning.
安妮
Anne.
我去帮你把衣服拿来
I guess I'll go get your coat, huh?
你知道我不会留在这的
Well, you know I ain't staying.
你知道我不会反对的
You know I ain't arguing.
你个老贱逼
You old cunt.
罗比  我不老
I'm not old, Robbie.
是爸爸
That's Dad.
爸爸  你怎么样
Hey, Dad. How's it going?
那个疯婆子在哪呢
Where's the crazy lady?
孩子的头发里有该死的麦片
Kid's got Rice fucking Krispies in his fucking hair.
这怎么回事
What's going on around here?
那些狗屁广告牌
And What the fuck is going on
到底是怎么回事  米尔德里德
with these fucking billboards, Mildred?
上面解释得够清楚了
Kinda self-explanatory.
我要听你给我解释
Well, why don't you just explain it to me?
那看来写得还不够清楚
Guess it ain't self-explanatory, then.
要知道  我希望让某些人把精力
Well, you know, I guess I wanted certain people's minds...
集中在本职工作上  仅此而已
kept on certain people's jobs, is all.
整整七个月了  他们那儿一点消息都没有
I hadn't heard from them in seven goddamn months.
我不得不说  自从我把广告牌立上
I tell you this, I've heard an awful lot from them...
就又听到了好一堆消息
since I put them billboards up.
你认为这让他们集中精力了
You think this has focused their minds? Mmm?
我告诉你这会让他们把精力放在哪
I'll tell you what it's focused their minds on.
他们会聚精会神  钻研怎么整你
It's focused their minds on how exactly are they gonna fuck you up.
你越是提高一件事的曝光度
The more you keep a case in the public eye,
这件事得到解决的几率就越大
the better your chances are of getting it solved.
所有指导书都是这么写的  查理
It's in all the guidebooks, Charlie.
这三块广告牌花了多少钱
How much these billboards cost?
大概是一辆牵引拖车的价钱
About the same as a tractor-trailer.
-你他妈笑什么呢  -没什么
- What the fuck are you laughing at? - Nothing.
被一个头发里有麦片的家伙嘲笑
Laughed at by a guy with fucking cereal in his hair.
-佩内洛普怎么样  -她挺好
- How's Penelope? - Huh? She's all right.
你为什么不请她进来
Why don't you invite her in?
省得让她坐在外面
Save leaving her sitting out there.
-她来了  -她在外面车里
- She here? - She's out in the car.
那就说得通了
Oh, that explains it.
-什么说得通了  -我就觉得闻到了什么
- That explains what? - I know I smelt something.
放了她
Let her go!
我想用下洗手间
I kinda need to use the bathroom,
不过要是不方便的话
but if it's inconvenient...
实际上  确实不方便  不是吗
actually, it is inconvenient, isn't it?
我知道不方便  我能忍住  没事的
I can see it's inconvenient. I can hold it. It's all right.
走过门厅  第一扇门就是
It's the first door down the hall.
你确定吗  我感觉自己来得不是时候
Are you sure? I feel like I'm... intruding.
赶紧去尿
Just go pee.
你来这里要说的都说了
Look, you said what you came to say,
那你为什么不和你的动物园女孩
so why don't you go get zoo girl...
滚出的我的房子  好吗
and get the hell out of my house, all right?
实际上  动物园项目
Um, actually, zoo-wise,
动物园在裁人
they were letting people go at the zoo,
不幸的是  是新晋员工最先被裁
unfortunately, and it was a case of "Last in, first out,"
所以  很不幸  动物园解雇了我
so yeah, unfortunately, the zoo had to let me go.
但残疾人骑马项目在招人
But they were looking for people down at the horse rides
来照顾那里的马
for the disableds to look after the horses down there.
所以我现在在那里工作
So I'm working down there now,
照顾残疾人骑的马
looking after the disableds' horses.
-一个字都别说  -我也没打算说
- Don't say a word. - I wasn't gonna say a word.
我也希望这件事没发生  你不觉得吗
You don't think I don't wish it had never happened?
我希望她还在  你不觉得吗
You don't think I don't wish she was still here?
我知道
I know you do.
广告牌没法让她死而复生  米尔德里德
Billboards ain't gonna bring her back, Mildred.
操19岁的姑娘也没什么用  查理
Neither is fucking 19-year-olds, Charlie.
是的
Yeah
但我清楚这一点
But I know that.
赶紧走
Just go.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
我是个差劲的爸爸
I'm such a shitty dad,
你是伟大的妈妈  行了吧
and you're such a great mom. All right.
那为什么  她死前一星期来问我
So how come, a week before she died...
能不能搬来和我一起住
she comes around asking if she can move in with me at my place?
因为她受不了
'Cause she couldn't stand
你们之间的争吵辱骂
the two of you bitching at each other no more,
-还有打架  -我不相信你
- fighting with each other no more. - I don't believe you.
我说  "不行  待在家  妈妈是爱你的"
And I said, "No. Stay at home. Your mom loves you."
我希望我没这么说过
Now I wish I hadn't.
因为如果我没说  她现在依然还活着
'Cause if I hadn't, she'd still fucking be here.
我不相信你
I don't believe you!
不用相信我
Don't believe me.
问水果麦圈男孩
Ask Froot Loop boy.
是真的吗
Is that true?
我不知道  妈妈
I don't know, Mom.
不  你知道
Yeah, you do.
怎么了
What's the matter?
没什么
Nothing.
拜托  别又是唐纳德·萨瑟兰
Oh, come on not, Donald Sutherland again.
这是怎么回事  唐纳德·萨瑟兰包了整季
What is this, frickin' Donald Sutherland season?
我喜欢他  喜欢他的头发
I like him. I like his hair.
头发
Hair?
这部片子里他小女儿去世了
This is the one where his little girl dies.
影片里的加分桥段
Always a plus in a movie.
说到身亡的孩子
Talking of dead kids,
那位放广告牌的女士怎么样了
what's happening with the billboard lady?
那个疯女人不讲道理
Oh, that kooz won't listen to reason.
她像茅坑里的石头又臭又硬
She's tough as an old boot.
那你为什么不利用她朋友呢
Why don't you just fuck her over through her friends then?
坑害她朋友
You know, why don't you fuck her friends over?
让她屈服
Bring her around that way.
她有你可以下手的朋友吗
She got any friends you can fuck over?
休息中
我被捕了  丹妮丝
卑鄙小人
Rat bastards.
艾彬镇警局
-混球  -什么
- Hey, fuckhead! - What?
迪克逊  她进来叫你混球
Don't say, "What," Dixon,
你不能应声"什么"
when she comes in calling you a fuckhead!
-你也不能闯进来  -闭嘴
- And don't you come in here... - Shut up!
你  过来
You, get over here.
不  你  过来
No! You, get over here.
-好吧  -什么  不行  迪克逊
- All right. - What? Don't! Dixon!
-怎么了  -你不能允许一个市民
- What? - You do not allow a member of the public...
在警察局里叫你混球
to call you a fuckhead in the station house!
我正在处理  我在用我自己的方式处理
That's what I'm doing! I'm taking care of it in my own way, actually.
现在给我滚开
Now get out of my ass.
海斯女士  请坐  有什么可以为你效劳的吗
Mrs. Hayes, have a seat. What is it I can do for you today?
丹妮丝·沃森在哪
Where's Denise Watson?
丹妮丝·沃森目前在押
Denise Watson's in the clanger.
-以什么罪名  -持有毒品
- On what charge? - Possession.
-什么毒  -两根大麻烟
- Of what? - Two marijuana cigarettes.
又粗又长
Big ones.
保释听证会什么时候
When's the bail hearing?
鉴于她有持有大麻的前科
I asked the judge not to give her bail...
我请求法官不给她保释的机会
on account of her previous marijuana violations,
而法官同意了
and the judge said, "sure."
你他妈的混蛋
You fucking prick!
你不能在警察局里
You do not call an officer of the law a fucking prick...
叫一个警官混蛋  海斯女士
in his own station house, Mrs. Hayes.
在其他任何地方都不行
Or anywhere, actually.
哪里学来的新招数  迪克逊
What's with the new attitude, Dixon?
你妈妈教你的吧
Your momma been coaching ya?
不是
No.
我妈妈
My momma...
没有教我
doesn't do that.
把广告撤下来  听到了吗
Take them down, you hear me?
迪克逊  你做得真棒
You did good, Dixon.
我知道
Yeah, I know I did.
就差一点
Almost got that.
有两个规则
The rules here are twofold.
不管什么时候
No kid can leave this goddamn blanket...
都不许离开这条毯子
at any goddamn time.
另外  每一个娃娃
And, every single one...
和每一个泰迪熊
of these dolls, and these teddy bears...
都必须钓到
has got to be hooked up.
现在  妈妈和我
Now, your momma and I,
虽然看上去不像
although it won't look like it,
但我们会看着你们的一举一动
we'll be watching every goddamn move you make.
所以我们看着你们的时候  最重要的就是
So the most important thing while we are watching you...
不许离开这条毯子
is that you do not, leave, this, blanket.
还有很重要的就是  不管什么时候
Next most important thing, you do not at any stage...
你们都不能
allow the fishing rods...
钩到你自己或者你姐妹的眼睛
to stick into you or your sister's eyeballs,
因为这样的行为
as this would be counter-productive...
会破坏整个行动
to the entire operation.
这样的行为会怎样
What would it be?
破坏整个行动
Counter-productive to the entire operation.
那么  童子军们
Then, troops...
开始钓鱼吧
start fishing.
不是吧
We are not.
走吧
We are.
钓到了
Yes.
宝贝
Hey, baby.
是啊  依然无人被捕
Yup, still no arrests.
我在想  怎么搞的
How come, I wonder?
因为没有上帝  整个世界都是虚无
Because there ain't no God, the whole world's empty,
我们对彼此做什么都无所谓吗
and it doesn't matter what we do to each other?
我希望不是
I hope not.
你这个不知道从哪里来的小家伙怎么那么漂亮
How come you came up here outta nowhere looking so pretty?
你该不会要我
You ain't trying to make me
相信轮回什么的吧
believe in reincarnation or something, are ya?
虽然你很漂亮  但你不是她
'Cause you're pretty, but you ain't her.
她被杀了
She got killed...
永远回不来了
and now she's dead forever.
但我真的很感谢你的出现
I do thank you for coming though.
要是我有吃的  一定会给你
If I had some food I'd give it to you.
我只带了一些玉米片
All I got is some Doritos,
它们可能会害了你  那零食有点尖锐
and they might kill you. They're kind of pointy.
那样的话我们会如何呢
Then where would we be?
是这样的  我正好在看我们上次
Yeah, so I, uh, just happened to be looking over our contract
拟定的合同
that we drew up back that time.
我发现
What I realized was I...
我发现尽管付款日是
I realized that although payment is to be made...
每个月的一号
on the first day of each month,
但是你上次付的第一笔钱其实是押金
the first payment you paid was actually a deposit.
是吧  就像我们说好的那样
Wasn't it? It's like we said.
所以  事实上
So, actually, in point of fact,
你现在还欠着
you're actually, behind in your payments now,
一个月的钱
by, yeah, a month.
那是
Yeah, that's, uh...
合同上就这么写的  你看看
It's what the contract says, looking over it and all.
律师也是这么说的
Lawyer says so too.
什么时候付下一笔钱  瑞德
When you need this next payment by, Red?
其实是  现在
Well, now, really.
或者
Or by...
到周五
Friday?
连律师和广告人都不能相信了
When you can't trust the lawyers and the advertising men,
美国堕落成什么样了
what the hell's America coming to, huh?
谁来找过你了  瑞德
Who got to you, Red?
威洛比
Willoughby?
-没人来找过我  -我信你才有鬼
- Nobody got to me. - My fat fucking ass.
-他快死了  米尔德里德  -我们都他妈会死
- He's dying, Mildred. - We're all fucking dying!
-瑞德  -帕梅拉  我们现在有点忙
- Red! - Hi, Pamela. We're a little bit busy at the moment,
-如果可以的话  -瑞德  瑞德  我知道
- if that's okay. - Red. Oh, Red, I know...
我知道你非常焦虑
I know you were real anxious about
-因为今早你要和海斯女士谈  -焦虑  没有
- talking to Mrs. Hayes this morning. - Anxious? No.
是吗  但其实  你不用再焦虑了
No, but that's the thing. There's no need to be,
因为你不会相信
because you won't believe it!
一个小个子墨西哥送货员刚刚把这个送来
Little Mexican delivery boy just dropped in with this.
-这他妈是什么  -我就说嘛
- What the hell is this? - I know!
是五千美金  你再猜猜纸条上写了什么
It's $5,000! And guess what the note says?
它写着这笔钱是帮海斯女士付广告牌租金的
It says to pay for the rental on Mrs. Hayes's billboards.
你能相信吗  所以我才闯进来
Can you believe it? That's why I butted in.
-谁送来的  -没有说
- Well, who's it from? - Well, doesn't say.
送货员呢
Well, where's the delivery boy?
走了
Well, he went.
你看到他是哪个公司的了吗
Well, did you see what company he was from?
-没有  -他穿着什么样的制服
- Well, no. - What kind of uniform did he have on?
就是一个普通的矮胖的墨西哥男孩
Well, he just looked like one of those fat little Mexican boys.
骑着自行车
On a bicycle.
我做错什么了吗
Did I do something wrong?
没有  小帕  你做得很好
No, no, Pam, you did good.
是的  帕梅拉  你真的做得很好
Yeah, Pamela, you did real good.
真的吗  太好了
Did I? Oh, great.
生活真是处处有惊喜
Ain't life crazy?
纸条上写了什么  瑞德
What's the note say, Red?
写着  "这些钱是用来资助
Says here, "This here money is to go towards the fund..."
米尔德里德·海斯的广告牌
"for Mildred Hayes's billboards,"
因为她不是这里唯一一个
"'cause she ain't the only one 'round here..."
讨厌蠢猪的人  署名  一个朋友"
"who hates the pigs. Signed, a friend."
看来现如今  人不能
I guess you can't be too picky
对谁是朋友太挑挑拣拣
about who your friends are these days, huh?
我需要一张收据  瑞德
I guess I'll be needing a receipt off you there, Red,
写上  下个月的账款已经全额付清
you know, saying the price of next month is paid in full and all.
当然  米尔德里德  当然
Oh, sure, Mildred, sure.
-现在就写  -好的
- Like now. - Oh, sure.
妈妈喝醉了吗  爸爸
Is Mommy drunk, Daddy?
没有  她只是有些偏头痛
No, no. She's just got a little migraine, is all.
一点  偏头痛
Little... Chardonnay migraine.
现在  你们两个不许再交头接耳了  好吗
Now, no more chit-chat outta you two, okay?
我们明天还可以不去上学吗  爸爸
Can we stay home from school again tomorrow, Daddy?
看看明天早上妈妈怎么说  亲爱的
We'll see what your mommy says in the morning, darling.
闭上眼
Eyes closed...
好好睡觉  好吗
and go to sleep, okay?
你闻上去不像吐过  真好
You don't smell like puke, which is good.
刷过牙了  我学到的小技巧
Aquafresh. Trick I learned.
女人啊
Women, huh?
但今天还是轮到你去马厩
But it's still your turn to clean the horseshit...
清理马粪
outta the stable, you know.
那些该死的马
Those fucking horses.
是你养的该死的马
They're your fucking horses.
我要一枪崩了那些该死的马
I'm gonna have those fucking horses shot!
我来清理吧  你这个小懒虫
I'll do it... you lazy bitch.
谢谢你  爸爸
Thank you, Poppa.
今天真是太美好了
That was a real nice day.
今天野战太爽了
That was a real nice fuck.
你雄风依旧  威洛比先生
You got a real nice cock, Mr. Willoughby.
你从哪个剧里看来的吗
Is that from a, play?
你雄风依旧  威洛比先生
"You got a real nice cock, Mr. Willoughby."
我想我可能在某个莎士比亚的剧里听过
I think I, heard that in a Shakespeare one time.
你个笨蛋
You dummy.
是奥斯卡·王尔德
It's Oscar Wilde.
奥斯卡·王尔德
Oscar Wilde.
别取下袋子
打电话报警
我亲爱的安妮
My darling Anne,
梳妆台抽屉里还有封更长的
there's a longer letter in the dresser drawer...
我用差不多整个礼拜写的遗书
I've been writing for the last week or so.
那封讲了我们  和我们的回忆
That one covers us, and my memories of us...
以及我一直多么爱你
and how much I've always loved you.
这封只讲今晚  以及更重要的  今天
This one just covers tonight, and more importantly, today.
今晚我我在马厩边自尽
Tonight I've gone out to the horses to end it.
安妮
我不会为我的行为道歉
I cannot say sorry for the act itself,
尽管我知道有那么一阵子
although I know that for a short time...
你会对我生气  甚至为这个恨我
you will be angry at me, or even hate me for it.
请别恨我
Please don't.
这不是那种"我孤身一人来到这世界
This is not a case of, "I came in this world alone..."
而今我将孤身一人离去"
"and I'm going out of it alone,"
或其他类似的愚蠢行径
or anything dumb like that.
我来这世界的时候并不孤独
I did not come in this world alone,
那时有我妈妈在
my mom was there.
我也不会孤独地离开这世界
And I am not going out of it alone,
因为你在
'cause you are there,
醉醺醺的在沙发上
drunk on the couch,
开奥斯卡·王尔德的"雄风"笑话
making Oscar Wilde cock jokes.
不  这是一次在某种意义上勇敢的自杀
No, this is a case, in some senses, of bravery.
不是说面对一颗子弹的勇气
Not the bravery of facing a bullet down.
接下来几个月的病痛
The next few months of pain...
远比一闪而逝的痛苦难忍
would be far harder than that small flash.
这种勇气是指我终于敢去权衡
No, it's the bravery of weighing up...
未来几个月仍然和你在一起
the next few months of still being with you...
仍然与你一同醒来  与孩子们一起玩耍
still waking up with you, of playing with the kids...
而与此同时  我也会在你眼中看到
against the next few months of seeing in your eyes...
我的痛苦对你的折磨
how much my pain is killing you,
我日渐衰竭的虚弱身体
how my weakened body, as it ebbs away,
以及你对我的照料
and you tend to it,
这是你对我的最后记忆
are your final and lasting memories of me.
我不要这样
I won't have that.
你对我的最后记忆将是  一家人在河边
Your final memories of me will be us at the riverside...
孩子们玩着愚蠢的钓鱼游戏  她们肯定作弊了
and that dumb fishing game, which I think they cheated at...
以及我在你体内  你在我上面
and me inside of you, and you on top of me...
几乎完全想不到黑暗将至
and barely a fleeting thought, of the darkness yet to come.
这样才是最好的  安妮
That was the best, Anne.
一整天完全没想起我的病
A whole day of not thinking about it.
就活在今天吧  宝贝
Dwell on this day, baby,
因为这是我生命中最好的一天
'cause it was the best day of my life.
替我亲亲姑娘们
Kiss the girls for me,
记住我永远爱你们
and know that I've always loved you,
如果有另一个世界  我也许会在那与你重逢
and maybe I'll see you again if there's another place.
如果没有另一个世界
And if there ain't,
自从认识你  我一直身处天堂
well, it's been heaven knowing you.
你的男孩
Your boy...
比尔
Bill.
欢迎来到密苏里州艾彬镇
艾彬镇警察局
*小女人  告诉我怎么了*
*Chiquitita, tell me what's wrong*
*你被你的悲痛困住了*
*You're enchained by your own sorrow*
*在你眼中*
*In your eyes*
*看不到对未来的希望*
*There is no hope for tomorrow*
*我多么不忍看到你这样*
*How I hate to see you like this*
*你无法否认这点*
*There is no way you can deny it*
这是闹哪出
What the hell's going on around here?
怎么
What?
你还站得住吗
Can you stand now?
还能
Yeah, I can stand.
我最好出去
I'd better get out there...
跟他们说几句
say something to 'em.
你不会再晕过去吧
You ain't gonna faint again, are ya?
我知道  现在最好的
I know that the best thing...
也是唯一能借以缅怀他的事
the only thing to honor that man's memory right now...
*然后他们听到主的声音*
*And they hear their master's voice*
就是去干活
is to go to work...
*他们跑去干活*
*They run to do their chores*
去当个
is to be a...
好警察
a good cop...
*应主的召唤*
*At master's calling*
像他一样考虑问题
to walk in his shoes...
做他天天做的事
and do what he did every day of his life.
*他们今晚的工作*
*Their job tonight... *
帮助人民
Help people.
*重写圣经*
*Re-write the Bible*
*为新一代的无信者*
*for a whole new generation of non-believers*
*牧师对人们大喊*
*The pastor screams out to the Crowd*
*有个必须被打倒的邪魔*
*"There's evil that must be put down!*
*它碰了那个小兵*
*And it touches the soldier boy.*
怎么了
What the hell's going on?
*他听取了主的声音*
*He heeds his master's voice*
*他的生命在呼唤*
*His life is calling...*
*亲爱的小兵*
*Sweet soldier boy*
*说话之人正在流血*
*The speaker's bleeding...*
你要去哪儿  小子
Where are you going, boy?
*他听到主的声音*
*He hears his master's voice*
*你听到主的声音了吗*
*Do you hear your master's voice?*
你这畜生  你搞什么
You fucking pig! What the fuck are you...
闭嘴
Shut up.
*召唤*
*Calling*
*像女妖塞壬的召唤*
*Like the Lady Siren's call*
*可爱的士兵沉默地瞪着天花板*
*Sweet soldier quiet, just staring at the ceiling*
看  瑞德  我也打白人
See, Red, I got issues with white folks too.
*他听到了主的声音*
*And he hears his master's voice...*
你看什么
Fuck you looking at?
*他听到了战争的召唤*
*He hears the call to war*
*塞壬在歌唱*
*The Siren's singing*
昨晚发生了一件不幸的事
Reports, sadly, have come in overnight,
密苏里州艾彬镇的局长  威廉·威洛比
that Chief William Willoughby of Ebbing, Missouri,
今早在他的院子里
took his own life early this morning...
结束了他的生命
in the grounds of his home.
加布里埃尔·弗罗斯特第一时间为您报道
This report just in from Gabriella Forrester.
悲剧今天降临在
Tragedy came calling today...
密苏里州艾彬镇的一个宁静的家庭
upon this quiet family home outside, Ebbing, Missouri.
这里住着威廉·威洛比局长  他妻子安妮
A home belonging to Chief William Willoughby,
还有他们的两个年幼的女儿波莉和简
his wife, Anne, their two young daughters, Polly and Jane.
威洛比局长似乎是
What appears to be a self-inflicted gunshot wound...
开枪自尽的
brought life to an end for Chief Willoughby,
他因工作勤劳
a man highly-respected in Ebbing...
为当地服务奉献  而在艾彬镇备受尊敬
for his diligence, and service to the community.
导致他今早自杀的原因
What led him to take his life in the early hours of this morning,
尚无法判断
it is too early to speculate.
有传言称是因为疾病
There were rumors of illness.
是否仅仅是因为工作压力
Could it simply have been the pressures of the job?
还是与我们两周前刚刚在这里进行过的那次
Or could it have something to do with a story we ran here,
关于那三块广告牌
just two weeks ago, of these billboards,
以及竖广告牌的女人  米尔德里德·海斯有关
and the woman who put them there, Mildred Hayes?
别  别
Don't. Don't!
好啊
Hi, there.
-你知道谁扔的罐子吗  -什么罐子
- You know who threw that can? - What can?
你呢  甜心  你知道是谁扔的吗
How about you, sweetheart? You know who threw that can?
不  我没
Uh, no, I didn't really...
谢谢啊  妈妈
Thank you, Mom.
有什么可以为你效劳的吗  先生
And what can I do for you today, sir?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
名牌上写着呢  你眼瘸啊
Name's on my tag, man. You hard of reading?
眼瘸
Hard of reading?
不是  这词不错  眼瘸
No, no. That's good, "hard of reading."
有点像耳背
Kinda like "hard of hearing,"
但实际上是  眼瞎
but it's actually "hard of reading."
听起来像玩文字游戏
Like a play on words or something, huh?
你想干什么
What do you want?
由于昨晚威洛比局长遭遇不幸
I've been sent down to take over from...
我受命接管这里
Chief Willoughby in light of last night's unfortunate event.
你开国际玩笑吧
You have got to be fucking kidding me!
你有证明的文书吗  先生
Do you have any documentation to prove that, sir?
你真的想看我的文书吗  渣滓
You really wanna see my documentation, fucker?
对  看他的文书
Yeah, see his documentation!
让他给你看看
Make him show it to you.
你们这群白佬垃圾就没活干吗
None of you cracker motherfuckers got no work to do?
那词不是种族歧视
Ain't that racist?
你的手怎么了  迪克逊警官
What happened to your hand, Officer Dixon?
我就是
Oh, I just kinda...
把人扔到窗外时
banged it up a little bit...
受了点伤
while I was throwing some guy out a fucking window.
日常工作
You know, the usual.
是吗
Oh yeah?
警校从来没教过我这个
They never taught me that one at the academy.
你上的哪所鬼学校
Which fucking academy you go to?
安吉拉·海斯的案子怎么样了
How are things coming along on that Angela Hayes case?
安吉拉·海斯
管好你自己
How's things coming along
别多管闲事  怎么样
on the mind-your-own-fucking-business case?
把你的枪和警徽
How are things coming along...
交出来怎么样
on the hand me your gun and your badge?
什么
What?
交出你的枪和警徽
Hand me your gun and your badge.
见鬼
Shit.
就在这儿
In here somewhere.
我找不到我的警徽了
Hey, listen, I can't find my badge.
真的  可能我弄丢了
No, seriously. Maybe I lost it.
把那个家伙从窗户扔下去时丢的
You know, dropped it when I was doing that window guy.
赶紧滚出我的警局
Just get the fuck out of my station house, man.
怎么了
What's going on?
我
I think I...
我被炒了
I think I just got fired.
炒了或者停职了  不确定是哪个
Fired or suspended, I'm not sure which.
被炒了
Fired.
需要帮忙就叫我一声
Anything I can help you with, just give me a holler.
叫米尔德里德·海斯
Give Mildred Hayes...
好
Okay.
你认识我吗
You know me?
只是通过电视和广播中知道你
Only from the TV... and the radio.
"欢迎来到密苏里"兔多少钱
How much these here "Welcome to Missouri" rabbits go for?
七块
Seven bucks.
上面写了价格
It's writ right on them.
现在应该不值七块了
Guess he ain't seven bucks now.
你到这来有什么目的
What you come in here for?
我到这来有什么目的
What I come in here for?
我可能是威洛比的朋友  如何
Well, maybe I'm a good friend of Willoughby's. How about that?
你是吗
Are you?
或者
Or, you know...
我可能是你女儿的朋友之类的
Maybe I was a friend of your daughter or something.
怎么样
How about that?
你是吗
Were you?
又或者
Or, uh...
也许我就是在她垂死时强奸她的人
You know, maybe I was the one who fucked her while she was dying.
怎么样
How about that?
你是吗
Were you?
不是
No.
我倒希望我是
I would have liked to.
我在报纸上见过她的照片
I saw her picture in the paper there.
迎宾铃救了你
Saved by the bell, huh?
砸坏了兔子  你欠我七块
You owe me seven fucking dollars for the rabbit.
看来你只能等下次我路过时
Guess you'll have to get it off me
从我身上搜刮出来  是吧  米尔德里德
next time I'm passing through, huh, Mildred?
我会的
Guess I will.
你不知道见到你我有多高兴
You don't know how glad I am to see you.
-什么  -那家伙想吓唬我
- What? - That guy was trying to scare me.
你没那么好吓唬
I wouldn't have said you scare easy.
还有比我更难吓唬的
I ain't the worst.
有什么需要我帮忙的吗  女士
What can I do for you, ma'am?
我丈夫昨晚在朝自己脑袋开一枪前
My husband left this for you before he shot himself
给你留了这个
in the head last night.
-我很遗憾  威洛比夫人  -是吗
- I'm sorry, Mrs. Willoughby. I... - Are you?
-你真心遗憾吗  -当然是的
- Are you really? - Sure, I am.
这对你来说是完美的结局  不是吗
Well, surely this is the perfect ending for you, isn't it?
证明了你的广告牌很成功
It's proof, that they were successful, those billboards of yours,
不是吗  死了一个警察
...isn't it? A dead policeman?
现在可以量化了
It's quantifiable now.
你是把这事怪在我头上吗
Are you blaming this on me?
没有
No.
这事我不怪你
I'm not blaming this on you.
我只是来把这封信给你
I just came to give you the letter.
我的女儿们在外面的车里
Now my little girls, are out in the car,
所以我最好别留在这聊天了
...so I'd better not stay and chat.
我不知道我们今天接下来要做什么
I'm not quite sure what we're gonna do for the rest of the day.
在你丈夫自杀当天
It's hard to know, what to do...
很难知道该做点什么
...the day your husband kills himself.
很难知道该做什么
It's hard to know what to do.
亲爱的米尔德里德
Dear Mildred...
我是死人威洛比
...Dead Man Willoughby here.
首先  我想为没抓到你女儿的凶手
Firstly, I wanted to apologize for dying...
就决定死去道歉
...without catching your daughter's killer.
这对我来说十分痛苦
It's a source of great pain to me,
一想到你认为我不关心此事
...and it would break my heart to think
我就心碎
you thought I didn't care,
因为我真的关心
'cause I did care.
只是有一些案子
There are just some cases...
你忙得焦头烂额
...where you never catch a break...
却在五年后
...then five years down the line...
有人在酒吧或牢房
...some guy hears some other guy...
听到另外一个人吹嘘此事
...bragging about it in a bar room or a jail cell...
整个案子因为愚不可及的行为
...and the whole thing is wrapped up...
而结案了
...through sheer stupidity.
我希望安吉拉的案子也会如此
I hope that might be true for Angela.
我真心这么希望
I really do.
第二  米尔德里德  我得承认
Second, I gotta admit, Mildred,
广告牌的主意真是太他妈棒了
...the billboards were a great fucking idea.
真是一步好棋
They were like a chess move.
尽管我的死跟它们
And although they had absolutely nothing...
怎么搞的  威洛比局长
没有任何关系
...to do with my dying...
但我确定镇里所有人
I'm sure that everyone in town...
都会认为有关系
...will assume that they did,
所以我决定支付广告牌下个月的租金
...which is why, for Willoughby's counter-move,
依然无人被捕
这是我回给你的一步棋
I decided to pay the next month's rent on 'em.
我想这样会很有趣
I thought it'd be funny,
在我入土后
you having to defend 'em...
你还要辩解一个月
...a whole nether month after they've stuck me in the ground.
你闹的笑话  米尔德里德  哈哈
The joke is on you, Mildred, ha ha,
我希望他们不会杀了你
...and I hope they do not kill you.
祝以上各事好运
So good luck with all that,
祝其它一切皆好运
...and good luck with everything else too.
我希望并祈祷你能抓到他
I hope and I pray that you get him.
你想让我去局里跟他们谈谈吗
Well, you want me to go down and talk to 'em?
不  我不希望你去局里跟他们谈
No, I don't want you to go down and talk to 'em.
会有人让他的妈妈
Somebody sending their goddamn mother...
去警察局找该死的警察谈吗
...down to talk to the goddamn police?
谈什么
To say what?
去说把你的工作还给你
To say, to give you your job back.
让那个黑人滚蛋
Get rid of that black guy.
他们不会谁的妈妈一句话
Ain't gonna listen to some guy's mother...
就挤走黑人的
...asking them to get rid of some black guy.
南方已经不一样了
Things have moved on in the South.
不该这样的
Well, it shouldn't have!
你被开掉了  他们会给你一笔钱吗
Will they give you some money for being laid off and all?
妈  我把别人扔出了窗户
I don't know what the compensation scheme is...
我不知道我还有什么补偿计划
...for when you throw a guy out of a window, Ma.
我该提前查的
Guess I should have looked into that beforehand.
让我谷歌一下
Let me Google that.
能有几千块吧
A couple of grand, maybe?
你在那干了三年
You been there three years.
不算在警校的五年
Not counting the five years at the academy.
六年
Six...
如果算上你留级的那年
...if you count the year you were held back.
你去哪
Where are you going?
不关你的事
None of your business.
去见你的情妇吗
Off to see your fancy woman?
-我没有情妇  -是啊  我清楚得很
- I don't got a fancy woman. - Yeah. I know.
你小心点
You wanna watch yourself.
不然你要怎样
Or...or...or you'll do what?
我打爆你的头  就是这样
I'll blow your goddamn head off, that's what.
那新闻你听说了吗
Oh, did you hear the news?
什么新闻
What news?
今天上午迪克逊把韦尔比
That Dixon guy threw that Welby guy...
从窗户中扔出去了
...out of his window this morning.
你在耍我吧
You're shitting me.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
不是耍我吧
You're shitting me
天啊  天啊
Holy shit! Holy shit!
天啊
Holy shit!
该死
Fuck!
把家里那个拿来
Go get the other one from the house.
我不该打电话给消防局吗
Shouldn't I call the fire department?
去他的消防局
Fuck the fire department.
这火可能就是他们放的
They probably started it.
别做蠢事
Don't do anything stupid!
卑鄙小人
Scumbags!
去他的  去他的卑鄙小人
Fucking, fucking scumbags!
该死
Shit!
好了
All right!
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
妈  你在做什么
Mom! What the hell are you doing?
好了  很好  走
Yeah. Okay. All right. Good. Come on.
算了  妈  求你了
Leave it! Ma, please!
来不及了
It's too late!
-罗比  -算了  求你了
- Robbie. - Leave it! Please!
罗比
Robbie!
两只手怎么样
How are those hands?
让我们单独聊聊  谢谢
Give us a minute here. Thank you.
我能问你几个问题吗
Can I ask you a couple of questions?
你想问什么都行
Can ask me all the questions you want,
把我放倒  逮捕我
...you take me down and arrest me.
我不会逮捕你  海斯夫人
I'm not gonna arrest you, Mrs. Hayes.
我没有理由逮捕你
I got nothing to arrest you for.
你现在还没有
Not yet you ain't.
我们不是敌人
We ain't all the enemy, you know.
我要折磨死那些混蛋
I'll crucify the motherfuckers.
你打算怎么做  米尔德里德
What are you gonna do, Mildred?
你要折磨死他们吗
You gonna crucify 'em?
对  我要折磨死他们
Yeah, I'm gonna crucify 'em.
你要折磨谁
Who you gonna crucify?
那些混蛋吗
The motherfuckers?
对  我要折磨死那些混蛋
Yeah, I'm gonna crucify the motherfuckers.
那么那些混蛋
Ooh, then those motherfuckers...
最好小心点  对吗
...better watch out, all right?
没错
Fucking A.
这是什么鬼
Oh, what's this shit?
尽管这些被烧毁的广告牌
And as sad as the spectacle...
显露出一副悲凉的景象
...of these burned out billboards might be,
考虑到威洛比局长的死
...in light of the death of Chief Willoughby,
本台首先怀疑
...this reporter for one...
这是否给三块广告牌
...wonders if this finally puts an end...
这一奇异事件画上了句号
...to the strange saga of the three billboards outside...
这根本不是句号  你个傻蛋
This doesn't put an end to shit, you fucking retard!
这只是开始
This is just the fucking start!
让这话上你的
Why don't you put that
《早安密苏里叫醒广播》如何  贱人
on your Good Morning Missouri fucking Wake Up broadcast, bitch!
我看电视知道
I see on the TV there were a bunch of fires...
昨晚镇子外面起了几场火
...lit outside of town last night.
几场火  是吗
Bunch of fires, huh?
就是那几块广告牌
Out at those billboards.
我当警察的时候
Yeah, well, back when I was a cop,
我倒是会关心是谁放的火
I would have been interested in who set those fires,
因为  严格来说  那是纵火罪
because, technically, that's arson.
但是  我已经不为那帮人卖命了
But, as I'm no longer employed by those people,
我就根本不在乎了  不是吗
I don't really give a good goddamn, now do I?
我去接
I'll get it.
迪克逊家
Dixon residence.
你好  迪克逊  我是塞德里克
Hey, Dixon, it's Cedric.
队长好  有什么消息吗
Oh, hey, Sarge. Got any news?
-关于什么的  -随便
- News about what? - I don't know.
比如我的工作之类的
About my job and stuff?
不是  什么
No. No. What?
不是
No. Uh...
安娜·威洛比刚刚过来送了一封信
Anne Willoughby, just dropped in a letter
比尔去世前写给你的
that... Bill wrote you before he died.
写什么了
What's it say?
我没读  迪克逊  又不是我的信
Oh, I haven't read it, Dixon. It's not my letter.
我...我这就过去取
Oh, well, listen, I'll... I'll come right down.
我十五分钟后到
Um, I'll be there in like 15 minutes.
我觉得这样可能不太好
Yeah, I d... I don't think that'd be such a great idea,
尤其是目前的情况  杰森
things as they stand, Jason.
你手头还有
You... you still got your keys
局里的钥匙  是吧
to the station house, though, right?
对
Yeah.
要不这样  你等大家下班回家之后
Well, why don't you, come and pick it up
再过来取信
after everyone's gone home?
我把它放你桌子上
I can leave it on your desk for you.
好的
Oh, okay.
还有
Actually, yeah, then
取完信  你可以
when you're done, you can... you can
把钥匙留下
just leave the keys
省得我们以后过去取了
you know, save us picking 'em up later.
好的
All right.
杰森·迪克逊警官
杰森  我是威洛比
Jason, Willoughby here.
很抱歉  我已经死了
I'm dead now. Sorry about that.
我有些事情想告诉你
There's something I wanted to say to you
一些在我生前没能说出口的话
that I never really said when I was alive.
我认为你具备成为一名
I think you've got the makings
优秀警察的素质  杰森
of being a really good cop, Jason.
你知道原因吗
And you know why?
因为内心深处  你是一个正派的人
Because deep down, you're a decent man.
我知道你觉得我不是这么想的
I know you don't think I think that,
但却是真的  傻瓜
but I do, dipshit.
不过  我确实认为你太暴躁了
I do think you're too angry, though.
我知道这都是因为你爸去世
And I know it's all since your dad died
你得照顾老妈  负责一切
and you had to go look after your mom and all.
但是如果你无法克制怒火  那么我认为
But as long as you hold on to so much hate, then I don't think...
你永远都不会成为
you're ever gonna become
那个我知道你想成为的角色
what I know you wanna become.
警探
A detective.
你知道要成为警探
Because you know what you need
你还需要什么吗
to become a detective?
我还知道当我这么说的时候你会退缩
And I know you're gonna wince when I say this...
但要成为警探  你所需要的  就是爱
But what you need, to become a detective... is love.
接招吧
Fuck 'em.
因为爱生静
Because through love comes calm,
静生思
and through calm, comes thought.
有时候  侦察是需要思考的  杰森
And you need thought to detect stuff sometimes, Jason.
你需要的就这些
It's kinda all you need.
你不需要枪
You don't even need a gun.
你也绝对不需要恨意
And you definitely don't need hate.
恨意永远都无法解决事情
Hate never solved nothing.
但静却能  思也能
But calm did. And thought did.
试试  试着改变一下
Try it. Try it just for a change.
没有人会觉得你是同性恋的
No one will think you're gay.
如果他们这么认为  那就以恐同罪逮捕他们
And if they do, arrest them for homophobia.
那样他们就该感到意外了吧
Won't they be surprised?
祝你好运  杰森  你是个正派的人
Good luck to you, Jason. You're a decent man.
你的霉运走得够多的了
And yeah, you've had a run of bad luck...
但是会改变的  我能感觉到
but things are gonna change for you. I can feel it.
*让你*
*Where thy mates*
*和亲爱的同伴*
*Of the garden*
*在那黄土中*
*Lie scentless*
*埋葬*
*And dead*
*我愿意*
*So soon*
*和你同往*
*May I follow*
冷静
Calm.
*当那爱人*
*And from love's*
*金色指环*
*Shining circle*
*失去宝石的光芒*
*The gems drop away*
*当忠实的心儿*
*When true hearts*
*憔悴*
*Lie withered*
*当心爱的人儿*
*And fond ones*
*死亡*
*Are flown*
*谁还愿意*
*Who would inhabit*
*孤独地*
*This bleak world alone*
*生存在*
*Oh, who would inhabit*
*这个凄凉的*
*This bleak world*
*世界上*
*Alone*
你们看到什么了
So, what'd you see?
我们从春天大街拐过来的时候
Well, when we turned the corner from Spring,
已经火光冲天了
the fire was already raging,
大概两秒之后  那个警察
and about two seconds later the cop fella,
-就从窗户跳出来了  -等下
- he just jumps out of the window. - Wait.
你们两个从春天大街拐过来
The two of you, turned the corner from Spring?
-你们两个之前在哪  -在...在我家
- Where were you before this? - Round...round my place.
你们两个是男女朋友吗
You two boyfriend and girlfriend?
萌芽阶段  你懂的
Early stages, you know.
是这样吗
Is that right?
我们约会了几次
We had a couple dates.
下周要不要跟我一起吃个饭
You wanna go out to dinner with me next week?
好  我跟你去吃饭
Yeah, I'll go out to dinner with ya.
但是我不跟你上床
But I ain't gonna fuck ya.
我...我也不会跟你上床的
Well, I... I ain't gonna fuck you neither.
应该不会
I guess.
烧伤患者  给他打了许多麻药
Burn victim. He's pretty heavily sedated.
哥们
Hey, man.
你还好吧  天啊
You doing okay? Jeez.
你被烧得挺重的
You got burned up pretty bad, huh?
不过你会没事的
You'll be okay though.
你...想不想喝杯橙汁
You, uh... you want a glass of orange juice?
我有吸管
I got a straw somewhere.
别哭
Don't cry.
你会  你会没事的
You'll be... you'll be okay.
对不起  韦尔比
I...I'm sorry, Welby.
-你认识我  -对不起
- You know me? - I'm sorry.
你对不起...你为什么道歉
You're sorry...sorry for what?
把你从窗户扔出去了
For throwing you out the window.
对不起  哥们
I'm sorry, man.
我不在乎
I don't care!
别他妈哭了  妈的
Stop fucking crying, God damn it!
盐分会把你的伤口弄坏的
The salt'll just fuck up your wounds.
我以为盐分能对你的伤口有好处
I thought salt was supposed to be good for your wounds.
我又不是他妈的医生
What am I, a fucking doctor?
谁啊
Who is it?
你不认识我
Oh, you don't know me really.
你想干什么
Well, what do you want?
我是为广告牌的事来的
I come about the billboards.
-牌子怎么了  -他们被烧掉了
- What about 'em? - They got burned up.
我知道
I know that.
我是最开始竖广告牌的人
I'm one of the guys who put 'em up in the first place.
我叫杰罗姆
Jerome.
你找我有什么事吗  杰罗姆
What can I do for you, Jerome?
通常投放这种大广告牌的时候
Well, when you put up a bunch of posters like that,
为了防止广告牌损坏或者烧毁
just in case any of them get screwed up or torn, they, uh
他们会给你留一个备份  你知道吗
give you a set of duplicates, you know?
不  这我还不知道
No, I didn't know that.
梯子本身已经很稳了  詹姆斯
Ladder's pretty steady as it is there, James.
没关系  我喜欢扶梯子
Oh... that's okay. I... I like holding ladders.
帮我消散忧愁
Takes me out of myself.
需要帮忙吗
Need a hand?
-你什么时候出来的  -一小时之前
- When'd you get out? - An hour ago.
法官没判
Judge threw it out.
他说拘捕报告填得不对
Said the arrest report weren't filled out right.
你好
Say, you...
放火烧警察局的不是你吧
Say, you didn't burn down the police station, did you?
不是  她整晚都跟我在一起
No, she was with me the whole night.
-什么情况  -说来话长
- Why would... - It's a long story.
还想贴韦尔比那张吗
Still wanna put up the Willoughby one,
他都已经死了
him being dead and all?
为什么不贴  他付的钱
Why not? He paid for it.
有道理
True.
*走开吧  蕾妮*
*Just walk away, Renee*
*你没看到我  跟着你回家*
*You won't see me follow you back home*
看这个混蛋
Look at this fucking asshole.
*我住的地方不是这样*
*On my block are not the same*
*不应该怪你*
*You're not to blame*
*在我被迫哭泣的*
*From deep inside the tears*
*泪水深处*
*I'm forced to cry*
*在我选择掩藏的*
*From deep inside the pain*
*痛苦深处*
*That I chose to hide*
*走吧  蕾妮*
*Just walk away, Renee*
*我不会再随你回家了*
*You won't see me follow you back home...*
-第一轮你请  -好
- First round's on you? - Yeah.
*雨点落下*
*Now as the rain beats down*
*打湿我疲惫的双眸*
*Upon my weary eyes*
*它亦为我潸然*
*For me it cries*
J·亚瑟餐厅
来吧
Well, here we are.
来
Here we are.
我喜欢芝士
I like cheesy things.
我要点个带芝士的
I'm gonna look for cheesy things.
好吧
All right.
他们是谁
Who's that?
我前夫
My ex-husband.
还有他19岁的女朋友
And his 19-year-old girlfriend.
-我们走吗  -不  不用
- You wanna leave? - No, no.
我们说好了的
Deal's a deal.
简直狂野
It was fucking wild, man.
我觉得我那一阵是失了智了
I think I was certifiably fucking insane for a while back there.
-什么时候的事  -九或十个月之前
- When was this? - About nine, ten months ago.
你自己吗
Were you on your own or what?
还有几个伙计
I had a couple of buddies with me.
-是吗  -嗯
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
他们也操她了
They fuck her too?
我觉得他们光看就兴奋了
I think they got their kicks just watching, you know?
-是吗  -对
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
她身材很火辣吗
Was she hot?
汽油一倒上  她就非常"火辣"
Once the gasoline kicked in she was hot.
真的  那让我更想上她了
I swear, I wanted to fuck her even more right then.
那个画面简直终身难忘
I don't know if I could get that out of my mind.
*我坐上了开往里士满的火车*
*I took the train to Richmond that fell*
*那时的记忆*
*It was a time*
营业中
*如此深刻*
*I remember, oh, so well*
汤炮酒吧
*南部陷落的那夜[1865年彼得斯堡战役]*
*The night they drove old Dixie down*
*警报声四起*
*And all the bells were ringin*
*南部陷落的那夜*
*The night they drove old Dixie down*
爱达荷州
*人们如此唱着*
*And all the people were singin', They went*
我可不会因为这种事完蛋
I ain't going down for that shit,
在那里的最后一天
...last fucking day down there.
*回想在田纳西  和我妻子在一起*
*Back with my wife in Tennessee*
*有一天  她告诉我*
*And one day she said to me...*
-他一直都在那吗  -谁
- He been there the whole time? - Who?
烧伤脸的这个  出去了又进来
Burnt face Jake. Keeps fucking walking up and down.
不知道  没有吧
I don't know. I don't think so.
*我管不上砍树了*
*Now I don't mind, I'm chopping wood*
*我也不在乎是否是不义之财*
*And I don't care if the money's no good...*
-再来一轮  -好
- Another round? - Yeah.
*需要的拿走  其余的留下*
* Just take what you need and leave the rest...*
*但他们不该把最好的拿走*
*But they should never have taken the very best*
八块
Eight bucks.
*南部陷落的那夜*
*The night they drove old Dixie down*
*警报声四起*
*And all the bells were ringin*
*南部陷落的那夜*
*The night they drove old Dixie down*
*人们如此唱着*
*And all the people were singin', they went*
伙计
Maestro.
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you with something?
什么
Excuse me?
你往这儿看了一晚上了
You keep looking over here all fucking night.
除非你有什么话想对我说
Now, unless you've got something to say to me,
不然别让我看见你那张疤脸
...why don't you take your burnt fucking face...
赶紧滚蛋
...and get the fuck out of here, okay?
-往里挪一下  -你要干什么
- No, I... scoot over. - What are you doing? What are you doing?
等一下  别急  别急
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
相信我
Just trust me, okay?
你喜欢看魔术吗
You like magic?
*我对着脚下的鲜血发誓*
*I swear by the blood below my feet...*
-相信我  -要变赶紧变
- Just trust me. - Just do the fucking trick, man.
好吧
Okay.
*警报声四起*
* And all the bells were ringin'... *
搞什么
What the fuck!
*南部陷落的那夜*
* The night they drove old Dixie down...*
行了
Hey.
可以了
Hey!
-够了  别打了  -你怎么回事
- Hey! That's enough now! - What's it to you, fucker?
他可是个警察
The guy's a cop, man. He's a cop.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
他又没戴警徽
He ain't wearing no badge.
我弄丢了
I lost my badge.
想不起来丢在哪儿了
Can't remember where I lost it.
你先挑的事  我可没动你
Hey, you started this, man! I didn't do shit to you!
是我先挑事
I know I started it.
我像个娘们似的挠了你
I scratched you up like a bitch.
没错
That's exactly fucking right.
*就像我的弟弟*
*And like my brother before me*
*我也会选择反叛*
*I took a rebel stance*
*他只有18岁  但勇敢又自信*
*Well, he was just 18, proud and brave*
我要去上个卫生间
I'm gonna go use the little boy's room.
你有什么想对我说的吗
You got something to say to me?
早知道  我们可以来个四人约会
If I'd known, we could have double dated.
又不是周末  小姑娘没宵禁吗
Doesn't shit girl have a curfew weeknights?
没有
No. No.
其实我待会儿要带她去看马戏表演
In fact, I was actually gonna take her to the circus later,
现在已经不需要了  他会杂耍吗
...but there's no need now. Does he juggle?
我只和他吃这么一顿
Look, I'm having one dinner with the guy,
因为他帮了我的忙
'cause he did me a favor, okay?
你用不着因为和侏儒一起吃饭
You don't have to explain yourself to me...
就跟我解释  米尔德里德
...'cause you're having dinner with a midget, Mildred.
我没在和你解释
I'm not explaining myself to you.
听上去就是解释
You kind of are.
我不是来笑话你的
Look, I didn't come over here to break your balls.
你想和多少侏儒约会都可以
You can date as many midgets as you want.
真的
No.
我是来跟你道歉的
No, I came over to say I was sorry, actually.
道什么歉
Sorry for what?
因为广告牌的事  还有一切
Sorry about what happened to your billboards and all.
都过去了
Yeah, well, it's all water under the bridge, I guess.
那就好
Good.
那就好  我当时喝醉了  但这都是借口
I'm glad. I was pretty drunk, but it still don't excuse it.
这些怨恨
All this anger, man.
佩内洛普那天跟我说
Penelope said to me the other day...
"怨恨只会招致更多怨恨"
"It just begets greater anger."
你懂吗
You know?
真的
It's true.
佩内洛普还知道"招致"
Penelope said, "Begets"?
对
Yeah.
"怨恨只会招致更多怨恨"
"It begets greater anger."
照顾好这位小姐姐  老兄
You take care of this little lady, okay, sport?
跟你比  算是大姐姐
Big lady compared to you, right?
-你还好吗  -我想回家了
- You all right? - I think I wanna go home now.
别说废话  詹姆斯
Don't give me any shit, James.
我们改天再约
We'll do it another night, all right?
还有必要改天吗
Why would I want to do it another night?
从我们到这儿
You've been...
你一直都表现的很尴尬
...embarrassed to be here ever since we arrived.
不是吧
Oh, for Christ sake.
不是我逼你来的  对吧
I didn't force you to come on this date, all right?
你逼我来的
You forced me.
逼你
F... forced you?
是约你出来
I asked you on a date. Wow.
你知道吗
You know...
我是没什么魅力
I know I'm not that much of a catch.
我是个卖二手车的侏儒
I know I'm a dwarf who sells used cars...
我还酗酒  我知道
...and has a drinking problem. I know that.
那你又算什么
But who the hell are you, man?
广告牌女士  你从来都不笑
You're that billboard lady who never smiles,
从来不对别人说一句好话
...never has a good word to say about anybody,
那天晚上又是谁
...and who, in the evening times,
把警察局给烧了
sets fucking fire to police stations!
结果我才是没有魅力的那个吗
And I'm the one who's not a catch?
要知道我完全可以不去帮你扶梯子的
You know, I didn't have to come and hold your ladder.
别闹大了
Now, don't make a scene.
你真的跟他说  "怨恨只会招致更多怨恨"
Did you really tell him, "Anger begets greater anger"?
是的是的
Oh! Yes! I did.
但不是我自己想的
I didn't make it up myself though.
不是我原创的
I can't claim that.
我从我看的一本书里
No, I read it, on a bookmark...
夹的书签上看到的
...which was in a book I was reading...
关于小儿麻痹症的书
...about polio.
还是马球  是哪个来着  就是讲马的
Polo. No. Which is the one, with the horses?
小儿麻痹症还是马球
Polio or polo?
-马球  -马球
- Polo. - Polo.
好好待她  查理
Be nice to her, Charlie.
听到了吗
You got that?
杰森
Jason!
-杰森  -杰森  -别看我
- Jason. Jason! - Don't look at me.
-别看我  -他们对你做了什么
- Don't look at me! - What have they done to you?
-别管我  妈妈  -你...
- Leave me, Momma! - Are you...
不  不要
No. No! Oh!
别把我...
Oh, don't let me...
折起来密封
证据
开门
Open up this door!
拜托  杰森
Please, Jason.
让我帮帮你  拜托了
Let me help you. Please.
你是我的孩子  开门啊
You're my baby boy. Open this door.
快开门
Please.
杰森  开门
Jason, please.
听话
Please.
快开开门
Please open the door.
爱达荷州
开门
Open up!
杰森
Jason!
我没事  妈妈
I'm all right, Momma.
一切会好起来的
It's all gonna be all right.
我不想给你假希望  好吧
I don't wanna get your hopes up, all right,
但有个家伙  我觉得...
but there is a guy, and I think...
他可能是凶手  我有他的DNA
he might be the guy. I got his DNA.
很多很多的DNA
Got a lot of it, actually.
我们说话这会  他们已经在检测了
They're making the checks, as we speak.
他在牢里吗
He's in jail?
不在  但是应该不难找
No, but he ain't gonna be hard to find.
你为什么觉得他是凶手
Why do you think he's the guy?
我听到他在谈论...
I heard him talking about...
去年年中对一个女孩做过的事
something he did to a girl the middle of last year.
我没听全  但...
I couldn't hear all of it, but...
但听着像安吉拉的遭遇
It sounded a lot like what happened to Angela.
然后他把我狠揍了一顿
And then he beat the crap out of me.
正因如此...
But because of that...
我拿到了很多他的基因
I got a bunch of his DNA.
所以  我想...
So, I wanted to...
尽快把这个消息告诉你
let you know sooner rather than later.
我不想让你放弃希望  好吗
I didn't want you to give up hope, you know?
我在坚持
I've been trying not to.
那...
Well...
你只能尽力而为
all you can do is try.
就像我妈说的...
As my momma says...
虽然不是说抱有希望  而是
not so much about hope as about...
我上学时候英语不好
well, I didn't used to be very good at English at school.
所以只能是"你只能尽力而为..."
So it was more "All you can do is try..."
"别把英语考得太差"
"to not be so crap at English."
因为如果你想当警察  必须学好英语
Because you need English, really, if you wanna be a cop.
其实做什么都需要英语好
If you wanna be anything, really.
除非你住在墨西哥之类的地方
Unless you live in Mexico or something.
谁想去那种地方
Who wants that?
迪克逊
Hey, Dixon?
谢谢你
Thank you.
你做得很棒  杰森
You did good, Jason.
干得真漂亮
You did real good.
但是他不是凶手
But he wasn't the guy.
什么
What?
没找到匹配的DNA
There was no match to the DNA.
同类型案件中没有找到匹配对象
No matches to any other crimes of this nature.
其实和所有案件都不匹配
To any crimes at all, in fact.
他没有案底
And his record is clean.
或许他只是在吹牛
Maybe he was just bragging.
-他不是在吹牛  -有这个可能
- He wasn't just bragging. - Well, that's as may be.
但安吉拉死时...
But at the time of Angela's death...
他都不在国内
he wasn't even in the country.
他在哪儿
Where was he?
我看了他的出入境记录
Well, I've seen his records of entry and exit to the States,
也和他的指挥官谈过了
and I've spoken to his commanding officer.
他不在国内  迪克逊  他不是我们要找的人
He wasn't in the country, Dixon. He ain't our guy.
不  他...
Uh, no, he...
他...他就算不是我们要找的人
He... he might not be our guy,
但他仍然做了其他混账事
but he still done something shitty.
这我确定
I know he did.
但不是在密苏里州干的
Not in Missouri he didn't.
那是在哪儿
Where was he?
这都是机密
That's classified information.
别这样  伙计
Oh, come on, man.
如果这家伙有指挥官
If the guy has a commanding officer,
如果这家伙九个月前回的国
and if the guy got back to the country nine months ago,
如果他去的国家还需要保密
and if the country where he was is classified,
你觉得他会去哪个国家
which country do you think he was in?
你知道...
Hey, you know...
我给你个提示
I'll give you a clue.
那里是沙漠区
It was sandy.
这线索并没什么用啊
That doesn't really narrow it down.
你需要知道的是...
All you need to know is that...
安吉拉·海斯的事不是他干的
he didn't do nothing to Angela Hayes,
所以...我们还得继续查
so... we're gonna keep looking.
好吗
All right?
我找到警徽了
I found my badge after all.
怎么搞的  威洛比局长
你好
Hello?
我是迪克逊
It's Dixon.
说吧
Tell me.
他不是凶手
He wasn't the guy.
米尔德里德
Mildred?
你确定吗
Are you sure?
事件发生时他都不在国内
He... he wasn't even in the country when it happened.
所以  不管他做了什么...
So, whatever he did...
都不是在这里做的
he didn't do it round here.
抱歉给了你假希望
I'm sorry I got your hopes up.
没事的  没事
Well, that's all right. That's all right.
至少我过了心怀希望的一天
At least I had a day of hoping,
是我这段时间来最好的一天
and that's more than I've had for a while.
我得挂了
I gotta go.
我有...
There was, uh...
我在想一件事
There was one thing I was thinking.
什么事
What's that?
我知道他没强奸你女儿
I know he ain't your rapist.
但我确定  他仍然是个强奸犯
He is a rapist, though. I'm sure of that.
你想对我说什么
What are you saying to me?
我知道他的车牌号
Got his license plate.
我知道他住哪儿
I know where he lives.
他住哪儿
Where's he live?
他住在爱达荷州
He lives in Idaho.
有点意思
That's funny.
我早晨要开车去爱达荷州
I'm driving to Idaho in the morning.
需要个伴吗
Want some company?
好的
Sure.
*我听过你如银般的歌唱*
*I heard you sing in tongues of silver*
*我听过你在夏日风暴中哭泣*
*I heard you cry on a summer storm*
*我爱你  你却浑然不知*
*I loved you, but you did not know it*
*我只能停止对你的思念*
*So I don't think about you anymore*
*如今斯人已逝  我却无法释怀*
*Now you're gone, I can't believe it*
*我只能停止对你的思念*
*So I don't think about you anymore*
*如果问题只有唯一解*
*If three and four was seven only*
*其它可能会置于何地*
*Where would that leave one and two?*
*如果爱只能孤独守望*
*If love can be and still be lonely*
*你我又该置身何处*
*Where does that leave me and you?*
*时间的巨轮永不停歇*
*Time there was, and time there will be*
*你我又该何去何从*
*Where does that leave me and you?*
*如果我有一匹鹿皮种马*
*If I had a buckskin stallion*
*我会驯服它  奔走远方*
*I'd tame him down and ride away.*
*如果我有一艘小船*
*If I had a flyin' schooner,*
*我会将它驶入白昼之光*
*Sail into the light of day*
*如果我能得到你无尽的爱*
*If I had your love forever*
*我会带它航行在白昼之光*
*Sail into the light of day*
*歌曲悠扬  景色宜人*
*Pretty songs and pretty places*
*我从未见过如此美景*
*Places that I've never seen*
*歌曲悠扬  精致脸庞*
*Pretty songs and pretty faces*
*向我讲述他们的乐事*
*Tell me what their laughter means*
*有人似乎总在哭泣*
*Some look like they'll cry forever*
*向我讲述他们的乐事*
*Tell me what their laughter means...*
-迪克逊  -怎么了
- Hey, Dixon? - Yeah?
你得告诉你点事
I need to tell you something.
是我放火烧的警察局
It was me that burned down the police station.
所以呢  除了你还能有谁
Why, who the hell else would it have been?
迪克逊
Dixon?
怎么了
Yup?
-你确定要这么做吗  -杀了这个家伙吗
- Are you sure about this? - About killing this guy?
不确定  你呢
Not really. You?
我也是
Not really.
我想我们可以边走边想
I guess we can decide along the way.
*歌曲悠扬  景色宜人*
*Pretty songs and pretty places*
*我从未见过如此美景*
*Places that I've never seen*
*歌曲悠扬  精致脸庞*
*Pretty songs and pretty faces*
*向我讲述他们的乐事*
*Tell me what their laughter means*
*有人似乎总在哭泣*
*Some look like they'll cry forever*
*向我讲述他们的乐事*
*Tell me what their laughter means*
三块广告牌